Guide to the Stanford University, Office of Development, Records SC0319
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Records, Accession ARCH-2007-025
  - Centennial Campaign Files
    - Planned Giving Training (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Planned Giving (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Venture Capitalists (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Venture Capitalists (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Campaign International Fundraising (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Centennial Campaign Lunch & Dinner February 10, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - Launching the Campaign (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - Matching Fund (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - Staff Memos (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - Backgrounds (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - Conference Attendance (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - Working Group (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - Report of the Development Office Task Force—Centennial Fundraising (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - Report fol 2 (Box 7, Folder 34)
    - Centennial Campaign Task Force (Box 7, Folder 35)
    - Position Papers (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - Other Board Lists (Box 7, Folder 37)
    - Centennial Campaign Staff Newsletter (Box 7, Folder 38)
    - First Centennial Symposium (Box 7, Folder 39)
    - Second Centennial Symposia (Box 7, Folder 40)
    - Third Centennial Symposia (Box 7, Folder 41)
    - Centennial Campaign—5/13 Freidenrich Vice Chair lunch (Box 7, Folder 42)
    - Leadership Gifts Prospects (Box 7, Folder 43)
    - Centennial Campaign: Major Gifts Program (Box 7, Folder 44)
    - Major Gifts Survey (Box 7, Folder 45)
    - Task Force File (Box 7, Folder 46)
    - C. T. F. Charts (Box 7, Folder 47)
    - Centennial Task Force Oman, Bennett, et al (Box 7, Folder 48)
    - Other Universities and the Campaign (Box 7, Folder 49)
    - Other Institutions: Cornell Study of Fundraising for Housing (Box 7, Folder 50)
    - The Harvard Campaign (Box 7, Folder 51)
    - Other Universities Campaign Information (Box 7, Folder 52)
    - Conway on Campaigning—Centennial Campaign (Box 7, Folder 53)
    - Brakeley, John Price Jones, Inc. Capital Campaigns Report (Box 7, Folder 54)
    - Fundraising in the ‘80's (Box 7, Folder 55)
    - Centennial Campaign: Fine Arts (Box 7, Folder 56)
    - Forecasting: Proposal Volume (Box 7, Folder 57)
    - Categories of Gifts (Box 7, Folder 58)
    - Campaign Notes—Recognition (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Early Strategy 1983—Feb. ‘85 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Trustees 12-9 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Centennial Grove (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Tracking System (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Gay Liberation Statue (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Donor Recognition (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Donor Recognition—2 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Other Universities Campaign Information (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - SJ Phone Responses (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Midwest NCC Follow-up (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Texas NCC May 1, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Centerpieces NCC (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - NCC Pens (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - SF NCC Pens (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - NCC Aug 90 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Back-up File (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Holzmueller Productions (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - NCC Costs (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - NCC Friday Evening and Brochure (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - NCC New York (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - NCC Seattle (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - NCC Los Angeles (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - NCC Attendance Analysis (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - NCC Dates (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Fundraising Results (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - NCC Budget/Costs (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Kile Ozier (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - NCC Logistics (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - NCC Invitation Task Force (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - NCC Project Outline (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - NCC Prism Notes (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - NCC Reports for RLB, AMB (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - NCC 100 Reports—Procedures (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - NCC Statistics & Final Report (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Staff Meeting/NCC Presentation 9/9/87 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Centennial Celebrations (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - NCC Seattle (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - NCC Dinner Attendance 1993 SF, NY, OC, Phoenix, SD, SJ, Portland, LA (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Centennial Celebrations (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Centennial Campaign Case Statement (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Campaign Communications (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - National Centennial Celebrations (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - NCC (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - NCC—School Reps Mtg (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - NCC Pay-Off (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - National Centennial Celebrations Schedules (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - NCC Panels—Staff Recommendations (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - Handouts (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - National Centennial Celebrations Volunteers (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - NCC's—National Centennial Celebrations 1989 (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - Centennial Case Statement Mailing—February, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - Case Statement Press Run (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - Case Statement Comments (Box 9, Folder 29)
    - President's Faculty Council on the Centennial Campaign (Box 9, Folder 30)
    - Centennial Campaign #1 (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - Campaign Planning 1985-1991 (Box 9, Folder 32)
    - Stanford—Centennial (Box 9, Folder 33)
    - Centennial Campaign—Planning Notes—Faculty Facilities (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Campaign for Stanford
    - Binders
      - Gift Opportunities (2 binders) (Box 10)
      - Centennial Campaign Coordinating Committee: Memo, minutes, etc 1983-84 (Box 10)
      - President's Centennial Discussion, Final Report for Staff Oct 1986 (Box 10)
      - Centennial Campaign—Program Plans, Marketing/Communication Plan (Box 10)
      - Consultative Group—Meetings Dec 1984-May 1985 (Box 10)
      - Briefing Book for National Major Gifts Committee (Box 10)
    - Assorted Centennial Campaign publications, Major Gift Program Volunteer Directory
  - Centennial Campaign Files
    - Binders
      - Inaugural—Campaign Cochairs January 7, 1986 (Box 11)
      - Book #1 and #2—Co-Chair Meetings & Steering Committee Meetings (2 binders) (Box 11)
      - Steering Committee—Campaign Cochairs Jan 86-Feb 88 (Box 11)
      - Steering Committee & Campaign Cochairs May 1988 (Box 11)
      - Co-chair Newsletter 6/86-6/88 (Box 11)
  - Pace Campaign
    - Binders
      - Major Gifts Reference Manual (Box 12)
      - Stanford "C" Campaign 1961-62 (Box 12)
      - Year-End Gift Reports 1957/58-1978/79 (Box 12)
      - Committee on Investment, Agenda & Minutes 1966-68 (Box 12)
  - Fundraising files—old
    - GSB—Fund Raising (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - GSB—Affiliate Programs (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - GSB—Alumni Association Growth Fund (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Grove Project (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Guaranteed Stable Costs Plan (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - "H"—Old (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - The Wilson Harwood Papers (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Hettinger, A. J., Jr.,(Foundation) (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Hitchcock & Chamberlain, Ltd. Ross F. Chamberlain Fund (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Human Biology (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Humanities and Sciences—General (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Donald M. Hummel, Mr. & Mrs. (Pottery Shack & Credit Bureau of Orange County, Inc.) (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - -I- (Old) (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - IDL Program (ARPA—Materials Sciences) (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Industrial Park (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Institute of International Relations (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - -J- —Old (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Joseph Jacobs (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - Journalism (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - -K- Old (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - Donald L. Kersting—Kersting, Brown & Co. (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - -L- —Old (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - Lake Lagunita (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - Law School—General—1968-1971 inclusive (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - Law School—General 1964-1967 incl. (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - Lectureships (Box 13, Folder 26)
    - Edmund W. Littlefield (Box 13, Folder 27)
    - Lytton, Bart (Box 13, Folder 28)
    - Mc-Mac—Old (Box 13, Folder 29)
    - "M"—Old (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Management Council—S.F. (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Manspeaker, Almon F. (Ctte. On Investments) (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Martzloff, Thomas H. (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Mathematics (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Medical Center Joint Planning Committee (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - School of Medicine (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - School of Medicine—General (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Russell Miedel—Old (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Centennial Campaign Files 1986-91
    - Centennial Planning 1984-86 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Centennial Planning 1984-86 (2) (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Consultative Group (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Field Division Managers (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Senate Committee 2/15 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Development Priorities Committee (formerly 4 C's & Prov. Dev. Com.) (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Centennial Campaign Coordinating Committee (4 C's) (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Campaign Proposed, Working Papers (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - Centennial Planning—1984 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - Binders
      - Prospectus (Box 14, Folder 1)
      - Volunteers (Box 14, Folder 2)
      - Undergrad. Education Opportunities Committee 1985 (Box 15, Folder 1)
      - Old Division Plans (Box 15, Folder 2)
      - Stanford Almanac & Stanford Review Columns by Dave Jacobson (Box 15, Folder 3)
      - Paton, G. Jeffry "Correlates of Successful College Fun Raising" 1982 (Box 15, Folder 4)
      - Liaison Team (Box 15, Folder 5)
      - Medical Development (Box 15, Folder 6)
      - Office of Development Budget 1990 (Box 16, Folder 1)
      - Policies (Box 16, Folder 2)
      - Office of Development Planning 1988-89 (Box 16, Folder 3)
      - Office of Development Planning 1990-91 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous folders on budget (Folder 16)
  - Memorial Church Restoration, Publications and Campaign for Stanford
    - Memorial Church Restoration
      - Mem Chu General Donor Recognition Plans (Box 17, Folder 1)
      - Memorial Church Reopening (Box 17, Folder 2)
      - 33708 (Box 17, Folder 3)
      - Mem Chu Donor Listings of $5K+ Donors (Box 17, Folder 4)
      - unlabeled (Box 17, Folder 5)
      - Memorial Church MG Letter (Box 17, Folder 6)
      - Memorial Church Gifts Since 11/91 (Box 17, Folder 7)
      - Certificate of Thanks (Box 17, Folder 8)
      - Memorial Services (Box 17, Folder 9)
      - unlabeled folder (Box 17, Folder 10)
      - Church Committee—Letters (Box 17, Folder 11)
      - Mel—Thank yous (Box 17, Folder 12)
      - Mel Lane Correspondence (Box 17, Folder 13)
      - unlabeled folder (Box 17, Folder 14)
      - Memorial Church Altar Project (Box 17, Folder 15)
      - Envelope with donation info and receipts (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Publications
      - The Art of Asking for Major Gifts (Box 17, Folder 17)
      - Stanford Graduate Fellowships Campaign (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - Campaign for Stanford
      - Determining Post-Campaign Assignments (Box 17, Folder 19)
      - Post-Campaign Volunteer Organization 1977 (Box 17, Folder 20)
      - Post-Campaign Plan RLB to DHP 1976 (Box 17, Folder 21)
      - Post Campaign Planning Critical Path Network Dec-May 1976-77 (Box 17, Folder 22)
      - Post-Campaign Planning 1974/75 (Background Data) (Box 17, Folder 23)
      - Post-Campaign Staffing 1974 (Box 17, Folder 24)
      - Staffing Projections (Box 17, Folder 25)
      - Communications Division Post-Campaign Staffing (Box 17, Folder 26)
      - Post-Campaign Staffing (Organization) (Box 17, Folder 27)
      - GSO Long Range Planning Bennett's Notes and Ideas (Box 17, Folder 28)
      - Faculty Volunteer Group Campaign for Stanford (Box 17, Folder 29)
      - Campaign Planning with John Young (Box 18, Folder 1)
      - Challenge Gift Specifications (Box 18, Folder 2)
      - A Campaign Plan for the Stanford Annual Fund (Box 18, Folder 3)
      - The Campaign for Stanford 1972-1977 Results and Data (Box 18, Folder 4)
      - Campaign Planning for the Medical School (Box 18, Folder 5)
      - Campaign Gifts/Professorships, Endowed Scholarships & Fellowships and Loan Funds (Box 18, Folder 6)
      - Matching Gift Needs & Estimates (Box 18, Folder 7)
      - Matching Program for Faculty & Staff (Box 18, Folder 8)
      - Meeting Held Monday, July 20, 1970 (Certain Individuals Concerned with Fund Raising at Stanford) (Box 18, Folder 9)
      - Five Year Plans (Box 18, Folder 10)
      - Project Directors (Box 18, Folder 11)
      - R-E-C-O-M-M-I-T-M-E-N-T Meetings (Box 18, Folder 12)
      - Campaign Receipt Projections by Donor, Type and Purpose Hughes/Andrews 72/73 Data (Box 18, Folder 13)
      - Gift Information—Campaign and General (Box 18, Folder 14)
      - Campaign Planning (Box 18, Folder 15)
      - Campaign (Box 18, Folder 16)
      - Campaign Ad Hoc Committee Prospecting (Box 18, Folder 17)
      - Campaign letters Announcement to Cabinet, Board/Governors, alumni board, etc. 6/71 (Box 18, Folder 18)
      - Campaign names, slogans… (Box 18, Folder 19)
      - Pearson speech to Cabinet and Trustees Ad Hoc Committee on Gift Program Campaign May 4, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 20)
      - Campaign Goals & Priorities (Box 18, Folder 21)
      - University Finances (Box 18, Folder 22)
      - Campaign Advisory Group (Box 18, Folder 23)
      - Campaign Strategy RW (Box 18, Folder 24)
      - Gift Opportunity System (Box 18, Folder 25)
      - General Campaign Information (Box 18, Folder 26)
      - Campaign Completion (Box 18, Folder 27)
      - Challenge Gift Proposal (Box 18, Folder 28)
      - Gift Table—1975-77 (Box 18, Folder 29)
      - Robert L. Conway Brakeley, John Price Jones Company (Box 18, Folder 30)
      - Robert L. Conway (Box 18, Folder 31)
      - Campaign Goals & Volunteer Org Chart (Box 18, Folder 32)
      - Campaign Project Group (Box 18, Folder 33)
      - Campaign Budget & Staffing Requirements (Box 18, Folder 34)
      - Case for Stanford Campaign Case Statement (Box 18, Folder 35)
      - Capital Campaign Gift Recording and Challenge Gift Earnings (Box 18, Folder 36)
      - Campaign for Stanford History and Statistics (Box 18, Folder 37)
      - Campaign Prospecting (Box 18, Folder 38)
      - Prospecting (Capital Campaign) (Box 18, Folder 39)
      - Bequest Statistics (Box 18, Folder 40)
      - Bequests (Distribution of Alumni & Non-Alumni) (Box 18, Folder 41)
      - Bequest Info (Box 18, Folder 42)
      - Post Campaign Organization (Box 18, Folder 43)
      - Joel Smith Cost Study, Long Range Planning, Marginal Analysis (Box 18, Folder 44)
  - Administrative Budget Files
    - Provost Presentation December 1974 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Outline of Presentation on Fundraising Performance & Budget Resources (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Forecasting Cabinet 3/13/78 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Forecasting 5/17/78 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Forecasting Cabinet 10/9/78 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Forecasting 6/29/79 Forecast to Cabinet & Financial Planning (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Forecasting Cabinet 11/12/79 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Cabinet 5/5/80 Forecasting (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Forecasting Report of Gifts Received 1972/73 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Forecasting Report of Gifts Received 1973/74 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Forecasting Report of Gifts Received 1974/75 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Long Range Forecast 1973/74 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Long Range Forecast 1975/76 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Long Range Forecast 1976/77 (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Forecasting Long Range Forecast 1977/78 (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - Gifts of $100,000 and over 1975/76 through 1979/80 (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - AB 3775 (Imbrecht) (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - Faculty Club Letters Requesting Membership—Staff (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - Faculty Club—Special Memberships Background (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - Faculty Club Special Membership—Background (Box 19, Folder 20)
    - Faculty Club 1970-1973 Special Membership (Box 19, Folder 21)
    - Faculty Club 1974/75 Special Membership (Box 19, Folder 22)
    - Faculty Club 1975/76 Special Membership (Box 19, Folder 23)
    - Faculty Club 1976/77 Special Memberships (Box 19, Folder 24)
    - Faculty Club 1977/78 Special Membership (Box 19, Folder 25)
    - Faculty Club 1979/80 Special Membership (Box 19, Folder 26)
    - Faculty Club Membership 1978/79 (Box 19, Folder 27)
    - Faculty Club 1980/81 Special Membership (Box 19, Folder 28)
    - Forecasting Report of Gifts Received 1978/79 (Box 19, Folder 29)
    - Forecasting Report of Gifts Received 1977/78 (Box 19, Folder 30)
    - Forecasting Report of Gifts Received 1976/77 (Box 19, Folder 31)
    - Forecasting Report of Gifts Received 1975/76 (Box 19, Folder 32)
    - Forecasting Report of Gifts Received 1973/74 (Box 19, Folder 33)
    - Cabinet (Box 19, Folder 34)
    - Harvard Cambridge, Mass. (Box 19, Folder 35)
    - Dartmouth, Hanover, N. H. (Box 19, Folder 36)
    - Cornell Ithaca, New York (Box 19, Folder 37)
    - University of California Fund Raising (Box 19, Folder 38)
    - Securities (Box 19, Folder 39)
    - Charge-Out of Land Resources Office Expense to Sale of Outside Properties (Box 19, Folder 40)
    - Research Activities (Box 19, Folder 41)
    - Projects—Miscellaneous (Box 19, Folder 42)
    - Professorships (Box 19, Folder 43)
    - Naming of Buildings (Box 19, Folder 44)
    - Indian Symbol (Box 19, Folder 45)
    - Hoover Institution (Box 19, Folder 46)
    - Gift Acknowledgement System Jayne Loughry (Box 19, Folder 47)
    - G-Plan (Box 19, Folder 48)
    - Frost Amphtheatre (Box 19, Folder 49)
    - Fellowships and Awards (Box 19, Folder 50)
    - Financial Aid (Box 19, Folder 51)
    - CEFA Bonds (Box 19, Folder 52)
    - Campus Soliciations (Box 19, Folder 53)
    - Yale New Haven, Conn. (Box 19, Folder 54)
    - Princeton Princeton, New Jersey (Box 19, Folder 55)
  - Administrative Budget Files and Study of Six Universities
    - Administrative Budget Files
      - Associates of Hoover Institution (Box 20, Folder 1)
      - Miscellaneous Universities (Box 20, Folder 2)
      - S-T-R-I-K-E May 13-June 2, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 3)
      - Comparative Costs of Fundraising (Box 20, Folder 4)
      - Analysis Biz—Law—Med Costs vs. $ Raised (Box 20, Folder 5)
      - Conflict of Interest (Box 20, Folder 6)
      - Cost of Publications (Box 20, Folder 7)
      - Formula Schools (Box 20, Folder 8)
      - Business School (Box 20, Folder 9)
      - Forecasting Non-Monetary Gifts $1000+ (Box 20, Folder 10)
      - Green Library Forecasting (Box 20, Folder 11)
      - Personnel Evaluation Process (Box 20, Folder 12)
      - Personnel Exempt Performance Evaluation Process (Box 20, Folder 13)
      - Analysis Headcount (Box 20, Folder 14)
      - Forecasting August to August Linear (Box 20, Folder 15)
      - Long Range Forecast 1980/81 (Box 20, Folder 16)
      - Forecasting Long Range Forecast 1979/80 (Box 20, Folder 17)
      - Forecasting Long Range Forecast 1978/79 (Box 20, Folder 18)
      - Forecasting Report of Gifts Received 1980/81 (Box 20, Folder 19)
      - Forecasting Report of Gifts Received 1979/80 (Box 20, Folder 20)
      - Matching Funds Reports—1 (Box 20, Folder 21)
      - Matching Funds Reports—2 (Box 20, Folder 22)
      - Matching Funds Reports—3 (Box 20, Folder 23)
    - Study of Six Universities
      - Comparative Study of Professional Schools December 1990 (Box 20, Folder 24)
      - Ivy Cost Comparison (Box 20, Folder 25)
      - Cornell (Box 20, Folder 26)
      - Harvard (Box 20, Folder 27)
      - Columbia (Box 20, Folder 28)
      - Penn (Box 20, Folder 29)
      - Survey of Comparable Schools to our 7 Schools (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - Old Files: Dave Jacobson, Ken Cuthbertson
    - Corson Report (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Development Plans 1957-1958 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Stanford Handbook (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - A Report to the Board of Trustees July 1954 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Stanford University Trustees' Bookshelf (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - A Discussion of Stanford's Needs and Opportunities 1960-1970 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Guide to Organization—Policies—Procedures (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Report of the Visiting Committee of the Associates of the School of Mineral Sciences Leland Stanford Junior University June 14, 1957 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - The Stanford Plan of Education for Medicine (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - A Program for Mineral Engineering at Stanford (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Student Life/Student Discipline (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Boards of Trustees and College Faculties (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Long-Range Program Graduate School of Business Stanford University (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Through the Looking Glass: A Radical Guide to Stanford (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Students and Society: Report on a Conference (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - Student Disruptions, etc. (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - Carnegie Commission on Higher Education—Report 1970 (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - Student Disruptions (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - The Campaign for Chicago (Box 21, Folder 19)
    - Student Papers from Cuthbertson's Class 1970 (Box 21, Folder 20)
    - H. Bruce Franklin (Box 21, Folder 21)
    - Student Unrest (Box 21, Folder 22)
    - Confrontation Politics in Higher Education 1969 (Box 21, Folder 23)
    - Clippings (Box 21, Folder 24)
    - Association of Independent California Colleges and Universities Symposium on Student Unrest and the Law (Box 21, Folder 25)
    - On Strike…Shut It Down! A Report on the First National Student Strike in U.S. History, May, 1970 (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - Centennial Campaign Files
    - Centennial Video (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Video Producers (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Near West Campus Video (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - KRON Documentary (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Training Film Project (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - TV Feasibility Study (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Incoming Mail (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Lucite Blocks (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Lucite Block Volunteer Memento Mailing List (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Centennial Campaign—Publicity (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Misc. (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Annual Fund—Statistics & Reports (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Campaign Leadership (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - Steering Committee 10/12/88 Overheads (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - Centennial Celebration 8/86- (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - Co-Chairs 8-29-88 (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - Co-Chairs 7-11-88 (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - Steering Committee 5-23-88 (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - Co-Chairs 5-11-88 (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - Co-Chairs 3-15-88 (Box 22, Folder 19)
    - Co-Chairs 2/9/88 (Box 22, Folder 20)
    - Steering Committee 2/9/88 (Box 22, Folder 21)
    - Co-Chairs 1-7-88 (Box 22, Folder 22)
    - Co-Chairs 11-20-87 (Box 22, Folder 23)
    - Co-Chairs 10-22-87 (Box 22, Folder 24)
    - Co-Chairs 9-28-87 (Box 22, Folder 25)
    - Steering Committee 9-28-87 (Box 22, Folder 26)
    - Co-Chairs 7-28-87 (Box 22, Folder 27)
    - Co-Chairs 6-25-87 (Box 22, Folder 28)
    - Centennial Campaign Co-Chair Meeting June 25, 1987 (Box 22, Folder 29)
    - Centennial Campaign Co-Chair Meeting 2/28/86 (Box 22, Folder 30)
    - Centennial Campaign Steering Committee Meeting 1/13/87 (Box 22, Folder 31)
    - Centennial Campaign Co-Chair Meeting July 28, 1987 (Box 22, Folder 32)
    - Steering Committee 5-15-87 (Box 22, Folder 33)
    - Co-Chairs 5-13-87 (Box 22, Folder 33)
    - Co-Chairs 4-17-87 (Box 22, Folder 34)
    - Letter to Board of Trustees and Trustees Meeting, 12/8/86 (Box 22, Folder 35)
    - Campaign Planning Background (Box 22, Folder 36)
    - Centennial Campaign Steering Committee Meeting 9/11/86 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Conference Call 7/8/86 8:00am (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Centennial Campaign Co-Chair Meeting 5/8/86 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - P. R. G. 5/8/86 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - First Meeting "Big Four" Co-Chairs January 7, 1986 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Centennial Campaign Steering Committee (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Campaign Co-Chairs Newsletter Updates September 1987—August 1988 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Supplies—Stationery (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Centennial Campaign Co-Chair Meeting 4/1/86 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Co-Chair Newsletters (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Corporate Chair Enlistment (Box 23, Folder 11)